<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Timbersmiths: Virginia Timber Framing on Timbersmiths Virginia Timber Framing</title><link>https://timbersmiths.com/</link><description>Recent content in Timbersmiths: Virginia Timber Framing on Timbersmiths Virginia Timber Framing</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://timbersmiths.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://timbersmiths.com/about-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://timbersmiths.com/about-us/</guid><description>Mission Statements Value – Timbersmiths places the highest value on our expertise and knowledge, we will always provide our services at fair market value. By providing our goods and services at their true value we enhance our ability to exceed our customers’ expectations and continue to grow Timbersmiths into a viable and sustainable company with dynamic objectives and sound financial projections.
Vision – Timbersmiths is committed to branding our name, products and services throughout Central Virginia and when practical to the Mid- Atlantic Region.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://timbersmiths.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://timbersmiths.com/contact/</guid><description>Contact Us 540-832-3988
pablo@timbersmiths.com</description></item><item><title>Gallery</title><link>https://timbersmiths.com/gallery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://timbersmiths.com/gallery/</guid><description>Mission Statements Value – Timbersmiths places the highest value on our expertise and knowledge, we will always provide our services at fair market value. By providing our goods and services at their true value we enhance our ability to exceed our customers’ expectations and continue to grow Timbersmiths into a viable and sustainable company with dynamic objectives and sound financial projections.
Vision – Timbersmiths is committed to branding our name, products and services throughout Central Virginia and when practical to the Mid- Atlantic Region.</description></item><item><title>Products</title><link>https://timbersmiths.com/products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://timbersmiths.com/products/</guid><description>Structural &amp;amp; Architectural Components Design and Restoration Professionals often seek out Timbersmiths to provide custom components for their projects which can be designed by us or made to the customer&amp;rsquo;s specifications. Timbersmiths can also provide TrimBür Frames to any existing structure.
TrimBür Frames If you wish to add timber frame touches to an already existing conventional structure, TrimBür Frames™ are available. Using the exact methods and materials as any traditional timber frame, TrimBür Frames™ can be crafted to accommodate any situation.</description></item><item><title>Services</title><link>https://timbersmiths.com/services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://timbersmiths.com/services/</guid><description>Custom Design All Timbersmiths timber frames start at the design process either working with individual owners, architects or contractors. It is exciting to start the process and sit down with the client and help them realize their dreams and fulfill their aspirations. The timber frames that we design represent more to our customer&amp;rsquo;s than just a home. They tend to be a lasting legacy, beautifully achieved for generations to enjoy. We want your custom hand-crafted timber frame home to be a rewarding endeavor for our customers.</description></item><item><title>Timber Frames</title><link>https://timbersmiths.com/timberframes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://timbersmiths.com/timberframes/</guid><description>Timber Frames Since 1978 Timbersmiths has led the revival of timber frame technology in central Virginia, bringing you the finest Timber Frames available at a reasonable cost. Timber framing provides a unique ability to connect to Virginia&amp;rsquo;s historic past, utilizing traditional methods, exposed timbers and fine craftsmanship. Timbersmiths treats every timber frame that we craft is an heirloom, which preserves a time honored legacy. We can design, craft and install any style of frame to meet any need.</description></item></channel></rss>